I'll be working this Christmas.
这个圣诞节我将去工作。
My job?
我的工作？
Santa Claus!
圣诞老人！
White beard and red clothes are optional.
白胡子和红衣服是可选的。
I'll be joining thousands of volunteers in Britain who go and help homeless and elderly people as well as poor children.
我将加入英国成千上万的志愿者队伍中，去帮助无家可归者、老年人以及贫困儿童。
Solidarity comes to life at this time of the year.
每年的这个时候，团结精神都会焕发生机。
It's cold and many people feel lonely.
天气寒冷，许多人感到孤独。
I'll be there for them.
我会在那里陪伴他们。
I was inspired by a woman in Scotland - Beatrice Cadell has just celebrated her 80th birthday and instead of presents for her, she asked her friends to buy toys.
我受到了一位苏格兰女性的启发——比阿特丽斯·卡德尔（Beatrice Cadell）刚刚庆祝了她的80岁生日，她没有要求朋友们送她礼物，而是让他们买玩具。
They'll be donated to a toy bank - free toys for children whose parents can't afford to buy them any.
这些玩具将被捐赠给玩具银行——为那些父母买不起玩具的孩子们提供免费玩具。
Cadell said: "Everyone that turned up to my birthday was absolutely brilliant!
卡德尔说：“出席我生日会的每个人都棒极了！
Somebody else can benefit.
其他人可以受益。
We don't need it.
我们不需要这些。
We're old."
我们已经老了。”
There are plenty of places which welcome a helping hand at Christmas.
圣诞节期间有许多地方欢迎志愿者的帮助。
The charity Crisis at Christmas, for example, has been looking for more than 10,000 volunteers to assist guests in their centres for homeless people.
例如，慈善机构“圣诞危机”（Crisis at Christmas）一直在寻找超过10,000名志愿者，来帮助其中心里无家可归的客人们。
Volunteers with specialist skills like dentists, hairdressers, lorry drivers and performers are particularly welcome.
具有专业技能（如牙医、理发师、卡车司机和表演者）的志愿者尤其受欢迎。
Another organisation, Community Christmas, is keen on volunteers who wish to offer companionship to lonely, elderly people on Christmas Day – it can be over a full lunch or just a cup of tea.
另一个组织“社区圣诞节”（Community Christmas）热衷于招募希望在圣诞节为孤独的老年人提供陪伴的志愿者——可以是一顿丰盛的午餐，也可以只是一杯茶。
They have a website with a location page so that good Samaritans can register their interest in helping out and find out more.
他们网站提供一个地址页面，以便好心的乐善好施者可以登记他们的帮助意愿并了解更多信息。
Scrooge is a character very much associated with this time of year.
斯克鲁奇（Scrooge）是一个与这个时节紧密相关的角色。
He's the central figure in A Christmas Carol, a classic by the English writer Charles Dickens.
他是英国作家查尔斯·狄更斯的经典作品《圣诞颂歌》中的核心人物。
Scrooge is a selfish man who only helps himself.
斯克鲁奇是一个自私自利的人。
In the world of volunteering, there's no Scrooge in sight.
在志愿者的世界里，看不到斯克鲁奇的身影。
We're all proud and happy Santas.
我们都是自豪而快乐的圣诞老人。
Merry Christmas!
圣诞快乐！